<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[ccc]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[ccc]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/ccc/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 23:20:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/ccc/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Clinical Compliance Concepts, Inc. is a Clinical and Technology based consulting company providing services to the Healthcare   Industry. Our consultants' experience, talents and training allow us to provide the right mix of clinical and technical skills available anywhere. We can fill your short-term or long-term needs. We're not fancy and slick. We offer only hard working people with the skills, experience, attitude, and drive to accomplish what you need. We know how to "roll up our sleeves" and get the job done.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ccc/9fba5c38-757d-4c71-b6a6-796750e731b4/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9fba5c38-757d-4c71-b6a6-796750e731b4</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 17:41:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/84659229-6e9e-41e7-9611-66afde15d0bd.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ccc/14ee58cd-aa29-4105-ace6-7149ac34c206/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">14ee58cd-aa29-4105-ace6-7149ac34c206</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 23:19:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>At Safety Net, we provide products that promote safety and health to  consumers and health care professionals. Safety Net helps to achieve  safer care environments for patients and residents in hospitals, long term  care and the community settings, specifically in regards to infection  control and prevention.     Infection Control & Prevention  Infection control and prevention has never been more important than it is today. The spreading of germs that cause illness is a concern for everyone.   The workplace...the gym...the classroom...in the hospital...   Regardless of how and where germs are transmitted, the potential risk of being exposed surrounds us everyday.     Traditional cleaning methods, such as a rag and bleach, are not enough.  These are most often used incorrectly and just spread the germs around.  Treat every room in your facility  with a system proven to kill disease-causing pathogens, including the difficult to kill, C. diff spores. Introducing the Halo Disinfection System from Sanosil International.  The Halo Disinfection System combines a choice of two patented 5% hydrogen peroxide-based disinfectants for use with the dry-mist dispensing HaloFogger™ as an easy-to-use, and affordable surface disinfection system. Unlike the ineffective “spray & wipe” approach and disinfecting technologies like UV, the Halo Disinfection System delivers hands-free, whole room surface disinfection at a 6-log kill rate that saves patients’ lives.      At the push of a button, the Halo dispenses a dry mist of atomized Halo™ Disinfectant into the air. The droplets fill the room and are drawn into every nook, crevice and corner, reaching surfaces that regular cleaning and disinfecting can’t. The Halo assures a homogenous distribution of disinfectant on all surfaces in the room, reducing the risk of cross-contamination of infectious diseases associated with using a rag, wipe or sponge.   Click here to learn more. Stemming the Tide of Ebola with Halo Technology Sanosil International has new technology that has been field tested and that we believe can be an integral part of the battle against Ebola.  Click the link below to learn more about this lifesaving technology.    Ebola vs. Halo Technology</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ccc/at-safety-net-we-provide-products-that-promote-safety-and-h/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a5bfa6bc-0a1c-4259-aa53-133b67488c0b</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 23:13:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wound Healing Treatment for Chronic Wounds]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Wound Healing Treatment for Chronic Wounds</h1><p>Wound Healing using Oxygen Treatment on venous stasis, leg ulcers, diabetic foot ulcers, decubitus ulcers, and pressure sores.</p><img src="http://www.ogenix.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/07/banner.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.ogenix.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">23cc78ab-c61b-440b-ae61-6f0e2f7e657a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 23:12:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Epiflo and the Halo are some of the new and innovative products we offer at CCC. </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ccc/62c6a19b-e55c-462d-aac0-120ad999e6c6/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">62c6a19b-e55c-462d-aac0-120ad999e6c6</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 23:07:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>